Coordinates for the targets
把所有目标的坐标
upload them into the missiles.
上传到导弹中去
Begin the launch countdown.
开始发射倒计时
How much time do you need to cancel the launch sequence?
取消发射程序需要多长时间?
I won't know for certain till I see how the targeting software is configured.
这个我不能肯定 要看定位程序是如何设置的
We're going to keep Bierko and his men out of here,
我们来挡住比耶科和他的人
so you can finish this.
你赶快把导弹搞定
Ten seconds to launch.
10秒后发射
it's done.
搞定了
The launch sequence is canceled.
发射程序取消了
You were never really going to let me go, were you?
你从来都没想过 真正放我走 是不是?
No.
是的
You were responsible for the deaths of David Palmer
你要为大卫・帕默
and Tony Almeida
托尼・阿尔梅达
and Michelle Dessler.
米歇尔・戴斯勒的死负责
I'm going after Logan.
我要去抓洛根
What do you mean,
你说
"going after Logan"?
"去抓洛根"是什么意思?
I'll fill you in  on the details later.
稍后再把详细情况告诉你
Right now, I need you to walk me through modifying some field communications equipment.
现在 我需要你帮我搞一套 外勤用的通讯系统
Who is this guy?
这个人是谁?
Morris O'brian,
莫里斯・奥布赖恩
Chloe's ex-husband.
科洛伊的前夫
I need some com unit modifications.
我需要修正一些小型通讯装置
Can you do that without talking?
你能闭口做到吗?
I could,
可以
but it would be a terrible waste of my charm.
但是这太浪费我的天才了
Jack Bauer's on his way here now.
杰克・鲍尔正赶往这里
He's going to confront  your husband directly.
他准备跟你丈夫当面对质
But Charles is leaving for the airfield immediately.
但查尔斯马上就要去机场了
You have to find a way to stall him.
你一定要想办法拖住他
There's a helicopter waiting for me.
有一架直升飞机正等着我
Let it wait.
让它等吧
I can't.
我做不到
Yes, you can.
不 你可以
You're the President.
你是总统
Aaron said the recording you had implicating the President was destroyed.
艾伦说 那个可以用来指控总统的录音 已经被毁掉了
Yes.
是的
Without it, you can't  mount a case.
没有它 你甚至都立不了案
I'm working with someone inside ctu.
我在和CTU中的某个人合做
They're setting up a digital uplink.
他们正在建立一条数字上传链路
If I can get Logan to acknowledge everything that he's done today,
如果我让洛根承认 今天他们所做的一切
it's going to be all the evidence we need.
那就会成为我们所需要的一切证据
I need to get on that chopper.
我要登上那架直升机
I don't see how that's gonna be possible.
我觉得这不太可能
If Logan doesn't confess,
如果洛根不承认
how far are you actually willing to go?
你会下多重的手呢?
As far as I have to.
看情况再定
The following takes place between 6Am and 7Am.
一下是发生于清晨6点至7点之间的故事
Here, let me get this for you.
来 让我来帮你
Watch your hair.
小心头发
Thank you.
谢谢
You're welcome.
不用谢
I got a flight suit.
我拿到飞行制服了
Go ahead.
请讲
Did you make it to the secret service outbuilding?
你进到特勤处外面那间房子了?
I think morris and i may have a way to pull the copilot from the flight.
我和莫里斯想到了一个 让副驾驶停飞的办法
What about the reassignment protocol?
把他调走怎么样?
Working on it.
正在做
Mike Novick will have to verify the pilot codes.
麦克・诺维克必须确认 那个飞行员的编号
It should take him about one minute.
大概需要一分钟
Chloe, hold on a second.
科洛伊 等等
I'm switching over to com.
我转到通讯器上
Okay.
好的
Do you copy?
听到没有?
I'll get back to you as soon as I'm on the chopper.
登上直升机后再跟你联系
Mike Novick's going to call.
麦克・诺维克会打电话过来
Morris.
莫里斯
Yes, sweetheart?
什么 亲爱的?
I need you to do one more thing.
需要你再帮一个忙
Some guy from central just called.
总部有人打电话过来
Says your packet's messed up.
说你的任务有一些冲突
I got that straightened out monday.
我星期一已经确认过了
I guess not.
我想没有
He wants to talk to you.
他想直接跟你说
Now?
现在?
Right now.
马上
He had me patch you through to the secret service outbuilding.
他让我带你去 特勤处外面的房子去
Mike.
麦克
I've delayed him as long as I can.
我已经尽可能的拖住他了
He'll be there in a few minutes.
几分钟后他就会出发
Have you heard anything from Jack Bauer yet?
杰克・鲍尔那有什么消息没有?
He should be in the secret service outbuilding.
他在特勤处外面的房子里
I'm sending him the necessary documents now.
我正把他需要的文档发给他
There's not much time.
没时间了
mike.
麦克
The reassignment protocol and authorization should be coming through to you.
你应该收到调令和授权书了
He'll need both.
两个都要给他
How are we doing for time?
还剩多少时间?
Hurry.
赶快
Hello.
喂
John.
约翰
Aaron.
艾伦
I thought you transferred out.
我还以为你已经被调走了呢
Not quite yet.
还没呢
Some guy from central called,
总部有人打过电话
said my packet's all messed...
说我的任务...
You will need this.
你需要这个
Don't worry about him.
我来处理他
Carruth has been relieved.
卡鲁斯换班了
I guess there was something wrong with his packet.
我想是他的任务安排有些问题
Ron Franklin.
罗恩・弗兰克林
There's my protocol.
这是我的文件
This is not bad,
不是很糟
but it needs to be more positive,like,
但我们还需要一些积极的消息
Jack Bauer is on the helicopter.
杰克・鲍尔已经登上直升机了
You have to find an excuse not to get on board.
你要找个借口不上直升机
Charles?
查尔斯?
Excuse me.
不好意思
Could I talk to youfor a second?
能和你谈一会儿么?
Absolutely.
当然
Will you excuse us for a second?
能不能等我一会儿?
I know it sounds silly,
我知道这听上去很蠢
but I didn't bring my medication.
可能忘记带药了
And I just, I just want to have it with me.
而 而我必须把它带在身上
Of course. Of course.
当然 当然
We'll send somebody back for it.
我们派人回去拿
No, no, no.
别 别 别
I don't want to delay you.
我不想耽误你
I'll be along later.
我稍后再来
Besides, Charles,
另外 查尔斯
I-I'm thinking that when you land,
我想当你着陆时
it would be better if I wasn't with you.
我最好不在你身边
Why?
为什么?
This is your moment, Charles.
因为那段时间是属于你的 查尔斯
I-I think that...
我觉得...
when you step out of that helicopter alone,
如果你在刚刚拯救完这个国家之后
after saving the country,
独自一人走出直升机
that is an image that history will never forget.
这将是历史无法忘记的一幕
All right.
好的
Thank you, Marti.
谢谢 玛莎
But don't be far behind me, now.
别太迟了
I won't.
不会的
Captain.
机长
I can fly this thing if I have to,
我一个人也可以驾驶飞机
which leaves you with one of two choices.
你有两个选择
You either do what I say and you live,
照我的话做 这样你就可以 好好的活下去
or you don't and you die for nothing.
或者不照我说的做， 白白丢掉性命
You understand me?
明白?
I want you to wait until I give you my command,
我要你听我讲完我的命令
then follow these instructions slowly.
并根据我的指示慢慢去做
You're going to disconnect your helmet from the communications system.
将你的头盔与通信系统断开
Then I want you to rip out the mic cable,
然后把话筒线拔出来
take your helmet off and stow it.
再把头盔摘下来
Do it now.
照做
I'll know if you deviate from your flight plan.
如果你不按飞行计划飞行 我会知道的
Mr. President!
总统先生!
I have a message for you from the white house!
我这里有一条白宫发给您的消息!
What the hell are you doing?
你到底在干什么?
Put these on!
把这个戴上!
You.
是你
This is Jack.Do you copy?
我是杰克 听到没有?
I'm here, Jack.
听到了 杰克
Where are you?
你在哪儿?
We just left the ranch.
我们刚刚离开农场
I have Logan with me.
洛根在我身边
Is morris standing by with the equipment?
莫里斯和他的设备准备好了没?
He's on his way.
他在路上
I'll let him know you're airborne.
我会告诉他你正在飞机上
Make sure the pilot takes heading 2-8-6 for two miles,
让飞行员沿航向2-8-6飞行2英里
then breaks south.
然后向南转
Captain!
机长!
I want you to follow heading 2-8-6 for two miles,
沿航向2-8-6飞行2英里
then break south.
然后向南转
Once you break south,
向南转之后
there should be an industrial park.
应该会看到一个工业区
There's an abandoned printing press facility that you can use.
有一个废弃的印刷厂你可以利用
I'll get back to you.
稍后跟你联系
Copy that.
收到
What are you trying to do, Jack?
你想干什么 杰克?
Whatever it is,
不管你想做什么
you know you won't get away with it.
你应该知道 你是脱不开身的
Are you going to kill me?
你想杀了我?
I suppose you want some sort of revenge.
我猜你是想来报仇
I understand that.
我知道了
Bad things happened.
一些我们不愿意看到的事情发生了
I didn't want them to happen.
我也不想它们发生
People who worked for me
那些为我工作的人
they-they went too far.
他们做得太过头了
They did things that they thought I wanted them to do,
他们以为 自己做的那些事情 是我让他们去干的
but they were wrong.
但他们错了
You have to understand.
你一定要明白
I have always acted in the country'sbest interest.
我所做的一切都是为了让这个国家 赢得最大的利益
But you're just trying to get even.
但你却要找我复仇
Do you realize what effect this will have on the american people?
你有没有意识到这样做 对美国人民会带来怎样的影响么?
This day has been trying enough,
今天已经够让人难受的了
and now the President is being attacked.
而现在总统又被人袭击
If you want to do what's right,
如果你想做正确的事
you will turn this thing around and go back.
就让飞机调头飞回去
Damn it, Bauer, say something!
该死 鲍尔 说话啊!
Hello.
你好
Morris.
莫里斯
Yes, love.
是 亲爱的
The helicopter is landing in an industrial park one mile due east of where you are.
直升机会在你的位置 往西1英里的一个工业区降落
Head over there.
快赶过去
Okay, now, I give this guy what we worked on,
好的 我就是把我做的东西交给他
and then I'm out, right?
然后就没我的事了 对吧?
Yes, but make sure you have him call me when you do the hand-off.
是的 但是你交给他的时候 一定要叫他给我电话
All right.
没问题
Thanks.
谢谢
Shut it down!
关掉!
your safety belt.
解开你的安全带
Move towards the door slowly.
慢慢靠到门边上去
Get out now.
快下来!
Move!
快!
Jack, maybe we can work something out.
杰克 也许我们能有别的解决办法
There's still time.
现在还来得及
What do you want?
你想怎样?
I can help you get away from here with enough money to start a new life,
我可以让你带着足够花的钱离开这里
maybe find that daughter of yours.
还可以带上你的女儿
Try to work something out.
我希望能有别的解决办法
Whatever you want,it's yours.
无论你要什么 都可以给你
You have my word.
我保证
Your word.
你保证?
Jack, I'm the President of the united states.
杰克 我是美国总统
I'm not carrying any weapons.
我不带武器的
Don't you make a sound.
不准出声
Give me the case.
把箱子给我
Jack Bauer.
杰克・鲍尔
I should have known that.
我早该料到是你
Modified equipment.
修复好的录音笔呢
Oh, that's President Logan,Jack.
哦 他是洛根总统啊 杰克
Get out of here.
你走吧
Chloe wants you to call her.
科洛伊要你打电话给他
Go.
快走
Yeah, Jack?
喂 杰克?
I have him.
得手了
All right.
好
I've just checked the response deployment.
我刚刚查了特别反应部队
You have less than ten minutes until they're on you.
10分钟不到他们就会来找你了
Fine.
好
Listen, Jack.
听着 杰克
I don't mean to put any added pressure on you,
我并不是故意要给你压力
but if you don't have a confession by then,
但是要是在那之前你拿不到他的认罪口供
we'll all be arrested for treason.
我们都会以叛国罪被捕的
Yeah, I know.
是 我明白
Is this some kind of broadcast?
这是广播用的吗?
What is this?
这是什么?
I would like to know.
我想弄清楚
Is this an assassination?
是不是要杀我?
A confession.
是认罪
Don't count on it.
你别指望了
I know you're good at extracting information.
我知道你很擅长榨取情报
I know that you're good at torture.
我知道你很擅长严刑逼供
I saw what you did with Walt Cummings.
我见识过你怎么对付沃尔特・卡明斯
I think you'll be surprised to find out
我猜你会很惊讶地发现
that I'm a little tougher than that.
我要比他强硬那么一点儿
Take a seat.
坐下
Chloe, it's Jack.
科洛伊 是杰克
Can you hear me?
能听见我说话吗?
Yeah, Jack.
是的 杰克
I want to make sure that you have good reception.
我要确认一下你那边接收状况良好
Who you talking to?
你在跟谁通话?
Are those your friends at ctu?
你在CTU的朋友吗?
You know you're putting them in danger, as well.
你知道你把他们也拖进了危险之中
Coming through fine, Jack.
通讯良好 杰克
Okay, good.
好
My people can't be far behind, Jack.
我的人不久就会赶来了 杰克
There's still time to get away.
你还有时间抽身
Take it.
接受我的条件吧
The plan involving the sentox nerve gas,
Sentox毒气计划
it was designed to fool the terrorists and the russians.
本意是设计恐怖分子和俄国人的
Whether or not you formulated the plan is irrelevant.
无论你原先是怎么计划的
You authorized it.
事情终归是你授权进行的
You're delusional.
你被人误导了
David Palmer uncovered evidence of this plan.
大卫・帕默发现了证据
When he started asking questions,
他开始追问
he was assassinated.
他就被暗杀了
Other people were killed to cover that murder up.
你又杀别的人来掩盖这起谋杀
Men and women who served this country with distinction;
那些对国家贡献卓著的人
people that I worked with;
我曾经的同事
friends of mine.
我的朋友们
No, you're wrong.
不 你错了
This is all a pack of lies.
这些都是谎言
The terrorists discovered your deception.
恐怖分子发现了你的骗局
And they deployed sentox nerve gas on american soil.
然后他们就在美国本土 释放Sentox神经毒气
Every american who died today
在今天的恐怖事件中
as a result of terrorist activity
遇害的每一个美国公民
is another murder that you're accountable for.
这些命案都要归咎于你
And before you leave here,
你不承认这些
you're going to admit it.
就别想离开这里
I suppose if you hurt me enough, Jack,
杰克 要是你打我打得够狠
I'll say whatever you want,
我就会说出你想要我说的任何话来
but that won't make it  the truth.
但是逼供说出来的决不是事实
And everybody who watches this will know that perfectly well.
看到这个视频的每一个人 都会很清楚这一点
What are the names of your co-conspirators?
你的同谋是谁?
There are no co-conspirators,
没有什么同谋
because there is no...
因为根本没有...
Walt Cummings,
沃尔特・卡明斯
Christopher Henderson,
克里斯托夫・亨德森
James Nathanson have all admitted to being part of this conspiracy!
詹姆斯・内特森 他们都承认参与了这起阴谋事件!
Now they are dead!
现在他们都死了!
Right before Christopher Henderson died
克里斯托夫・亨德森死之前
he acknowledged that there were others!
供出了还有其他同谋的人!
What are their names?
是谁?
A man will say anything under torture.
一个人被刑讯就什么话都会说出来
This won't mean a thing.
这些没有任何意义
Mr. Logan, I'm not going to torture you,
洛根先生 我不会拷打你
but you are going to tell me what I want to know.
但是你必须得告诉我 我需要知道的信息
Or so help me god,
否则 上帝帮助我
I will kill you.
我会杀了你
A year and a half ago,
一年半之前
I was warned that my life was in danger
我收到警告
by someone within the government.
我的性命受到政府里某个人的威胁
I was told the only  way I could stay alive
只有制造我已经死亡的假象
was to create the illusion that I was dead.
我才能保住性命
I was forced to deceive people that I loved.
我不得不欺骗我所爱的人
My only daughter will never forgive me.
我唯一的女儿永远也不会原谅我
As I see the depth of your corruption unfold,
当我看到你的腐败行径
I have no doubt that you are that source of danger.
我确信你就是那个危险人物
David Palmer was a great man.
大卫・帕默是位伟人
And he was a great President.
他也是位伟大的总统
He was also my friend.
他也是我的朋友
He tried to warn me about you
他曾尽力提醒我防范你
and now he is dead.
而现在他死了
Other people tried to help me
别人尽力帮助过我
and they are dead, too.
而他们也死了
So, Mr. Logan,
洛根先生
I hope you understand
我希望你明白
I have absolutely nothing to lose.
我现在没什么好失去的了
You are going to be held accountable
你该为今天发生的一切事情
for your part of everything that happened today.
担负你的那份罪责
You are not going to be able to hide behind the presidency.
你再也不能躲在总统职位的后面
Right here, right now,
现在 就在这里
you are going to face justice!
你要面对正义的审判!
And make no mistake about this,
你不要搞错了
this is personal.
这纯粹是个人行为
And if you think for a second that I am scared to put a bullet in your brain,
如果你以为我不敢给你的脑袋来一枪
you don't know me.
你就太不了解我了
I'm going to ask you one last time,
我最后一次问你
who are your co-conspirators?
你的同谋是谁?
You have until the count of three,
我数三下
or I will kill you.
然后我就杀了你
One...
1...
you make me a martyr,
你会让我成为一个殉国者
I'll go down in history with lincoln and kennedy,
我会跟着林肯和肯尼迪的名字名垂青史
but you'll go down with john wilkes booth and lee harvey oswald.
而你就会跟约翰维克斯・布斯和 李・哈维・奥斯瓦德之流并论
Is that what you want?
你希望这样的结果吗?
Two!
2!
You're a man of honor.
你是个有荣誉感的人
How can you assassinate a President of the united states in front of the entire world?
你怎么能在全世界面前杀害美国总统?
If you love your country,
如果你爱国
you won't pull the trigger.
你就不会扣扳机
Three!
3!
You can't do it, can you?
你做不到 不是吗?
No, Jack,
不 杰克
it's all right.
不要紧
Jack,
杰克
It's all right that you can't.
你做不到 这不要紧
I'm the President.
我是总统
Jack, they're here.
杰克 他们来了
Lay flat on your stomach!
趴到地上!
Put your hands out in front of you!
伸出你的手!
Extend your arms!
伸开双手!
Mr. President,are you all right?
总统先生 你没事吧?
I'm fine.
我没事
I actually feel sorry for that man.
实际上我为这个人感到遗憾
He's delusional.
他被人误导了
It would be better
你们现在最好
if he were put in some sort of solitary confinement for the time being.
把他单独监禁起来
Jack Bauer wasn't able to get the President to confess,Mrs. Logan.
杰克・鲍尔没能让总统坦白 夫人
I'm sorry.
对不起
Why not?
怎么会呢?
What happened?
发生了什么事?
I'm not sure of the details.
具体我也不太清楚
Bauer's in custody.
鲍尔已被逮捕
Gentlemen.
先生们
Thank you.
谢谢你们
Thank you very much,ladies and gentlemen.
非常感谢 女士们先生们
That will be all.
到此为止吧
Thank you so much.
非常感谢
-If I could just get you to come this way. -Thank you.
-请走这边  -谢谢
David...
大卫...
-Marti, don't do this to me now. -You killed him.
-玛莎 别这样  -你杀了他
You killed him.
你杀了他
-You're a murderer. -Stop.
-你这凶手  -别这样
You are!
凶手!
You're a criminal!
你是凶手!
My wife is not well.
我夫人不太舒服
-Would you please escort her? -Get off me!
-请你护送她离开  -放开我!
Don't you touch me!
别碰我!
-Don't you touch me! -Escort her into the hangar, please.
-别碰我!  -请护送她进机棚
You don't know what he did!
你们不知道他的所作所为!
He's not fit to be President!
他不配做总统!
It is a sacrilege for him to be even speaking David's name!
他不配说大卫的名字
Don't...!No!
别...不!
I want to make sure that she's all right.
我去看看她怎么样
Has the hangar been cleared?
机棚安全吗?
Yes, sir.
是的 总统先生
All secure.
很安全
-It's empty. -Good.
-里面没人  -很好
Let them know that I'll be back in a moment.
跟他们说我一会儿就回来
Yes, Mr. President.
是 总统先生
You're not wearing some kind of listening device, are you?
你身上没带窃听装置 是吧?
What are you talking about?
你说什么啊?
I have to watch you now, Marti.
我不得不提防你 玛莎
You said that I was a good liar,
你说我是个骗子
but I am nothing compared to you.
但和你比起来差远了
Charles...! Stop it!
查尔斯...住手!
Stop it!
住手!
Charles...
查尔斯...
Yeah, Marti.
好的 玛莎
Tell me the truth.
跟我说实话
You're hurting me.
你弄痛我了
You don't know what pain is.
你不知道什么叫痛
I'm on to you, Marti.
我比你更痛 玛莎
I should've seen it from the first,
一开始我就应该知道
but I wanted to believe that you still cared for me.
但我愿意相信你仍然关心我
Making love to me was just a ploy, wasn't it?
跟我做爱只是你的计策 是吧?
Took a lot of planning to get Jack Bauer on that helicopter.
精心计划让杰克・鲍尔上了直升机
You were part of that plan, weren't you?
而你是计划的一部分 是吧?
It was your job to delay me, wasn't it?
你负责拖延时间 是吧?
Wasn't it?
是不是?
Please...
放开我...
They used you so Jack Bauer could get to me.
他们利用你 以便让杰克・鲍尔抓到我
Come on, Marti.
说吧 玛莎
Admit it,
承认吧
you were part of it.
你和他们是一伙的
Yes.
是的
Why?
为什么?
Why...?
为什么要帮他们?
Because you killed David Palmer.
因为你杀了大卫・帕默
I told you I didn't realize that was going to happen.
我说过 我没想到那会发生
Your people killed him to protect you.
你为了自保而杀了他
You covered it up,that's just as bad.
然后你又掩盖这事情 这同样糟糕
I covered it up because I had to.
我不得不
Oh, and then others died to cover that up.
这么多人丧命都是为了掩盖这事情
That's right, for the good of the country.
对 这是为了国家利益
You sold nerve gas to terrorists.
你向恐怖分子出售神经毒气
You're insane.
你是疯子
You're insane!
神经病
I did it for the good of the country as I saw it at the time.
为了国家的利益 我做了眼下正确的决定
You're such a hypocrite.
你这伪君子
After your little performance this morning,
你今天早上所做的事情
you're in no position to call me a hypocrite.
决定了你没有资格叫我伪君子
And I will tell you something else
我告诉你
if you blow up like this one more time...
如果你再发神经...
I will fill you so full of drugs,
我就给你足量的药吃
you won't even remember your own name.
到时候你连自己的名字都想不起来
And then I will ship you off to an asylum
然后把你送到精神病院
and you can stay there for the rest of your life.
让你在那里度过余生
Are we clear?
听明白了?
Now clean yourself up,you're a mess.
自己好好收拾一下 弄得一团糟
My fellow americans,
同胞们
this has been a terrible day in the history of this country
今天是这个国家历史上可怕的一天
and yet at the same time,
但同时
a triumphant day,
也是成功的一天
because in the end,
因为最终
we won a significant victory over the forces of chaos and terror.
我们战胜了混乱和恐怖 取得了重大的胜利
We have preserved and protected our way of life,
我们保存 也保护了我们的生存方式
despite the loss of innocent american lives.
虽然有许多无辜的美国人为此丧生
I'll start the transmission in one minute.
在一分钟内将传送设置完毕
Is the attorney general there?
司法部长在吗?
I'm here, ms. O'brian.
我在 奥布赖恩小姐
I certainly hope this recording is as important as you claim it is.
我当然希望这录音象你所说的那样重要
Chloe, what's this about?
科洛伊 怎么了?
I set up a conference call with the attorney general.
我接通了给司法部长的会议电话
He's on speakerphone now.
他现在正在听电话
Are you serious?
你说真的?
I'm very serious.
真的
Mr. Attorney general,
司法部长先生
this is karen hayes,
我是凯伦・海因斯
homeland security.
国土安全部的
Bill buchanan, ctu.
我是CTU的比尔・布坎南
Sir, I apologize.
长官 我向你道歉
Ms. O'brian placed this call without authorization from me.
奥布赖恩的行为未经过我的授权
I'm sorry I had to do that.
对不起 我不得不这么做
We had to do things under the radar to protect you all in case things went wrong.
我们必须秘密行事 以避免发生意外
In case what things went wrong?
避免发生什么意外?
I think it would help if I just played the recording.
还是让我先放录音吧
What recording?
什么录音?
It's a conversation that took place five minutes ago
是五分钟前的一段对话的录音
between the President and his wife.
总统夫妇间的对话
How could you possibly have a recording of something like that?
你怎么会取得这样的录音呢?
Sir,
长官
an agent named Jack Bauer
一个名叫杰克・鲍尔的探员
placed a listening device on the President shortly before this conversation.
在谈话前将录音装置装在了总统身上
Bauer?
鲍尔?
Isn't he the one that's under arrest?
就是刚刚抓起来的那个?
I'm going to play the recording now.
我现在就播放录音
I don't want to listen to it.
我不想听这录音
Ms. O'brian, at the very least,
奥布赖恩小姐 无论如何
this constitutes an egregious violation of privacy,
这构成了对隐私的侵犯
and we're talking about the President.
而被侵犯人是美国总统
...'Cause you killed David Palmer.
...因为你杀了大卫・帕默
I told you, I didn't realize that was going to happen.
我说了 我没想到那会发生
Your people killed him to protect you.
你为了自保而杀了他
You covered it up,
你派去灭口的人
that's just as bad.
又被你灭口
I covered it up because I had to.
我不得不
Oh, and then others died to cover that up!
这么多人丧命都是为了掩盖这事情
That's right, for the good of the country.
对 这是为了国家利益
You sold nerve gas to terrorists.
你向恐怖分子出售神经毒气
You're insane.
你是疯子
You're insane!
你疯了
A poet once said,
有位诗人说过
"No man is an island."
"没有人是一座孤岛"
On a day like this,
从今天所发生的一切
we can feel the truth of those words.
我们可以感受到这些字的真正含义
Any untimely death is a tragedy.
任何英年早逝都是一场悲剧
Yet some men embody such greatness of character
更何况是如此高尚的人
that their death serves as a unifying force for those who remain behind.
他们的死能够让我们活着的人 凝聚在一起
David Palmer was such a man.
大卫・帕默就是这种人
A great President,
一位伟大的总统
a great american
一名伟大的美国人
and on a more personal note
对我个人来说
a wonderful friend.
也是一位好友
He'll be missed...
人们会以...
-...more than words can express... -Holtzman.
-我无法言表的悲情来悼念他...  -霍兹曼
Yes, sir.
是
We take this moment to remember with appreciation...
我们应该饱含感激来铭记这一刻...
with all due respect,Mr. Attorney general,
恕我冒昧 司法部长先生
are you sure this isn't some kind of mistake?
这当中没有什么误会吧?
Yes, sir.
是 先生
I understand, sir.
明白 先生
-I'll do exactly as you say. -...Combination of wisdom,
-我会照您说的去办  -集智慧...
strength and moral courage,
力量和勇气于一身...
this country might have not survived in its present form.
如果没有他的无私奉献 这个国家就不会有今天
It's very appropriate that David Palmer will be laid to rest in arlington cemetery,
将大卫・帕默安置于阿林顿国家公墓 是再合适不过的
for he was a soldier in the truest sense.
他是一名追求真理的斗士
He was a man whose courage rose in direct proportion to the threats his country faced.
在国家遭受威胁之时 他所表现出来的勇气让人惊叹
In closing, I would ask
最后 我想请求
that the country observe a national day of mourning
将某一天作为国家悼念日
for one of the greatest americans this nation will ever see.
用来悼念这位 美国有史以来最伟大的公民
Thank you very much.
非常感谢
Federal marshall.
司法执行官
-Would you please come with us? -What the hell do you think you're doing?
-请跟我们走一趟?  -你认为自己在做什么?
You came very close to disrupting my speech.
你差点破坏我的演讲
On behalf of President Logan,
我代表洛根总统
I wish to thank you all very much for joining us.
非常感谢你们能够参与这场仪式
I am sorry, but out of respect for today's...
我很抱歉 不过今天的仪式到此...
those are ridiculous accusations.
那些指控都是无稽之谈
Excuse me.
抱歉
If I may, sir?
可以吗 先生?
You've probably never seen one of these, Mr. President.
你可能没有看到 总统先生
It's a micro-transmitter.
是微型发报机
Agent clark, arrest these men
克拉克探员 逮捕这些人
and get them the hell out of here.
并将他们赶出这里
I'm sorry Mr. President.
抱歉 总统先生
-We have our orders. -You take...!
-我们已经收到命令  -你应该...!
You take your orders from me.
你应该听从我的命令
Not anymore.
不再是了
After you, sir.
这边走 先生
Attention!
立正!
Aim,fire!
举枪 鸣枪!
Give me a second.
稍等
-Hey. -Hey.
-来了  -是的
Thank god you're safe.
谢天谢地你没事
Everything's going to be all right.
一切都会好起来的
Jack, when I heard you kidnapped the President...
杰克 当我听到你绑架了总统时...
I was just trying to get him to give me a direct confession.
我只是想让他直接招供
Jack...
杰克...
how much longer do you need to stay here?
你还会在这里呆多久?
Not much longer.
不会很长
They can debrief me tomorrow.
他们明天会听我的报告
You sure?
是么?
I can't believe you're really,
真是难以置信
you're really here.
你真的在这里
Agent Bauer,excuse me,
鲍尔探员 打扰一下
but there's a call for you from your daughter.
不过你女儿正打电话来找你
From my daughter?
我女儿?
Yes, sir. A kim Bauer.
是的 金・鲍尔
It's been put through to a land line just inside that door.
被转到那扇门后面的 固定电话上了
Thank you.
谢谢
I'll be right back.I promise.
我马上就回 我保证
Take as long as you need.
去和她谈吧
I'm not going anywhere.
我就在这里等你
I love you.
我爱你
I'll be right back.
马上就回
Hey, kim?
嗨 金?
Any word on Logan?
洛根说什么没有?
No.
没有
My guess is he'll try to cut a deal.
我猜他是想讲什么条件
He'll resign without a fight in exchange for clemency.
他想要平静的辞职 不希望引起一场争斗
He doesn't deserve clemency.
他并不值得同情
No, but the country doesn't deserve a long impeachment process,
是的 不过这个国家可不愿意看到 一场漫长的弹劾议程
either,with everything that's happened.
以及一切由此带来的麻烦
In any event,
不管怎样
we can expect hal gordon to be sworn in as President soon.
可以想象哈尔・加德纳尔将会 宣誓成为新一任总统
Which means this will probably be the last time I see this place.
也就是说 这会是我 最后一次看到这个地方
I don't think so.
我不这样认为
Not if I have anything to do with it,
我会尽量想办法留住你
and I will.
而且我肯定会
You'll be back here running ctu.
你会回来继续掌管CTU
Thank you.I appreciate that.
谢谢 非常感谢
When I came in here last night to save the day,
昨天晚上我来接管这里时
I was a little bit condescending and tactless,
我有一点狂妄自大和不成熟
to say the least.
退一步说
I had no idea what you were up against.
我根本不知道你所面对的是什么
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
No. No need to apologize.
不 不需要道歉
Mistakes were made.
过去的就让它过去吧
You were right to come in with a firm hand.
你现在应该振作起来
Well, I better go.
好了 我该走了
Karen.
凯伦
I was thinking of getting some breakfast before going home.
我想回家之前先去吃点早餐
I have to go over to division for one last briefing.
我要到总部去进行最后一次简报
Bureaucracy.
制度上的要求
Rain check?
改日吧?
Sure.
没问题
Chloe,really good work today.
科洛伊 今天干得不错
You, too.
你也一样
I found this in edgar's possessions.
我在埃德加的东西中 找到了这个
I thought you should have it.
我想应该给你
Thanks.
谢谢
Hey.
嗨
What's all this, then?
这是什么?
A friend of mine who died today.
今天死去的一个朋友
You, um,
你 嗯
do you want to talk about it?
你想跟我谈谈么?
Yeah? Come on.
好的? 来吧
Jack?
杰克?
Oh, my god.
天哪
Agent davis,Jack Bauer's missing!
戴维斯 杰克・鲍尔不见了!
Attention, all units.
所有人注意
We have a missing agent:Jack Bauer.
有一名探员失踪了 杰克・鲍尔
I repeat, we have a missing agent: Jack Bauer.
重复 有一名探员失踪了 杰克・鲍尔
...The lower level.
放下其他事情
Put three men on perimeter search.
派三个人到周围去找找
Report back.
返回报告
You surely must be aware, Mr. Bauer,
你一定很清楚 鲍尔先生
that China has a long memory.
中国人的记性向来很好
Only 18 months ago,
18个月前
you invaded our territory and killed our consul.
你侵犯我们的领土并杀死我们的领事
Did you really think that we would forget, hmm?
你真的以为我们会忘记了?
I know how this works.
我知道你们想干什么
I need to make one phone call.
我只想打一个电话
Please...
求你了...
just one phone call.
就打一个电话
Kill me.
杀了我
Just...
杀...
kill me.
了我
Kill you?
杀了你?
You're far too valuable to kill, Mr. Bauer.
你这么有价值 杀了你就太可惜了 鲍尔先生